scrcpy 3.0.2 <https://github.com/Genymobile/scrcpy>
Usage: F:\Projects\Hackathon\Neurotech\scrcpy\scrcpy-win64-v3.0.2\scrcpy.exe [options]

Options:

    --always-on-top
        Make scrcpy window always on top (above other windows).

    --angle=degrees
        Rotate the video content by a custom angle, in degrees (clockwise).

    --audio-bit-rate=value
        Encode the audio at the given bit rate, expressed in bits/s. Unit
        suffixes are supported: 'K' (x1000) and 'M' (x1000000).
        Default is 128K (128000).

    --audio-buffer=ms
        Configure the audio buffering delay (in milliseconds).
        Lower values decrease the latency, but increase the likelihood of buffer
        underrun (causing audio glitches).
        Default is 50.

    --audio-codec=name
        Select an audio codec (opus, aac, flac or raw).
        Default is opus.

    --audio-codec-options=key[:type]=value[,...]
        Set a list of comma-separated key:type=value options for the device
        audio encoder.
        The possible values for 'type' are 'int' (default), 'long', 'float' and
        'string'.
        The list of possible codec options is available in the Android
        documentation:
        <https://d.android.com/reference/android/media/MediaFormat>

    --audio-dup
        Duplicate audio (capture and keep playing on the device).
        This feature is only available with --audio-source=playback.

    --audio-encoder=name
        Use a specific MediaCodec audio encoder (depending on the codec provided
        by --audio-codec).
        The available encoders can be listed by --list-encoders.

    --audio-source=source
        Select the audio source (output, mic or playback).
        The "output" source forwards the whole audio output, and disables
        playback on the device.
        The "playback" source captures the audio playback (Android apps can
        opt-out, so the whole output is not necessarily captured).
        The "mic" source captures the microphone.
        Default is output.

    --audio-output-buffer=ms
        Configure the size of the SDL audio output buffer (in milliseconds).
        If you get "robotic" audio playback, you should test with a higher value
        (10). Do not change this setting otherwise.
        Default is 5.

    -b, --video-bit-rate=value
        Encode the video at the given bit rate, expressed in bits/s. Unit
        suffixes are supported: 'K' (x1000) and 'M' (x1000000).
        Default is 8M (8000000).

    --camera-ar=ar
        Select the camera size by its aspect ratio (+/- 10%).
        Possible values are "sensor" (use the camera sensor aspect ratio),
        "<num>:<den>" (e.g. "4:3") or "<value>" (e.g. "1.6").

    --camera-facing=facing
        Select the device camera by its facing direction.
        Possible values are "front", "back" and "external".

    --camera-fps=value
        Specify the camera capture frame rate.
        If not specified, Android's default frame rate (30 fps) is used.

    --camera-high-speed
        Enable high-speed camera capture mode.
        This mode is restricted to specific resolutions and frame rates, listed
        by --list-camera-sizes.

    --camera-id=id
        Specify the device camera id to mirror.
        The available camera ids can be listed by:
            scrcpy --list-cameras

    --camera-size=<width>x<height>
        Specify an explicit camera capture size.

    --capture-orientation=value
        Set the capture video orientation.
        Possible values are 0, 90, 180, 270, flip0, flip90, flip180 and flip270,
        possibly prefixed by '@'.
        The number represents the clockwise rotation in degrees; the flip"
        keyword applies a horizontal flip before the rotation.
        If a leading '@' is passed (@90) for display capture, then the rotation
        is locked, and is relative to the natural device orientation.
        If '@' is passed alone, then the rotation is locked to the initial
        device orientation.
        Default is 0.

    --crop=width:height:x:y
        Crop the device screen on the server.
        The values are expressed in the device natural orientation (typically,
        portrait for a phone, landscape for a tablet).

    -d, --select-usb
        Use USB device (if there is exactly one, like adb -d).
        Also see -e (--select-tcpip).

    --disable-screensaver
        Disable screensaver while scrcpy is running.

    --display-id=id
        Specify the device display id to mirror.
        The available display ids can be listed by:
            scrcpy --list-displays
        Default is 0.

    --display-orientation=value
        Set the initial display orientation.
        Possible values are 0, 90, 180, 270, flip0, flip90, flip180 and flip270.
        The number represents the clockwise rotation in degrees; the "flip"
        keyword applies a horizontal flip before the rotation.
        Default is 0.

    -e, --select-tcpip
        Use TCP/IP device (if there is exactly one, like adb -e).
        Also see -d (--select-usb).

    -f, --fullscreen
        Start in fullscreen.

    --force-adb-forward
        Do not attempt to use "adb reverse" to connect to the device.

    -G
        Same as --gamepad=uhid, or --gamepad=aoa if --otg is set.

    --gamepad=mode
        Select how to send gamepad inputs to the device.
        Possible values are "disabled", "uhid" and "aoa".
        "disabled" does not send gamepad inputs to the device.
        "uhid" simulates physical HID gamepads using the Linux UHID kernel
        module on the device.
        "aoa" simulates physical gamepads using the AOAv2 protocol.It may only
        work over USB.
        Also see --keyboard and --mouse.

    -h, --help
        Print this help.

    -K
        Same as --keyboard=uhid, or --keyboard=aoa if --otg is set.

    --keyboard=mode
        Select how to send keyboard inputs to the device.
        Possible values are "disabled", "sdk", "uhid" and "aoa".
        "disabled" does not send keyboard inputs to the device.
        "sdk" uses the Android system API to deliver keyboard events to
        applications.
        "uhid" simulates a physical HID keyboard using the Linux UHID kernel
        module on the device.
        "aoa" simulates a physical keyboard using the AOAv2 protocol. It may
        only work over USB.
        For "uhid" and "aoa", the keyboard layout must be configured (once and
        for all) on the device, via Settings -> System -> Languages and input ->
        Physical keyboard. This settings page can be started directly using the
        shortcut MOD+k (except in OTG mode) or by executing: `adb shell am start
        -a android.settings.HARD_KEYBOARD_SETTINGS`.
        This option is only available when a HID keyboard is enabled (or a
        physical keyboard is connected).
        Also see --mouse and --gamepad.

    --kill-adb-on-close
        Kill adb when scrcpy terminates.

    --legacy-paste
        Inject computer clipboard text as a sequence of key events on Ctrl+v
        (like MOD+Shift+v).
        This is a workaround for some devices not behaving as expected when
        setting the device clipboard programmatically.

    --list-apps
        List Android apps installed on the device.

    --list-cameras
        List device cameras.

    --list-camera-sizes
        List the valid camera capture sizes.

    --list-displays
        List device displays.

    --list-encoders
        List video and audio encoders available on the device.

    -m, --max-size=value
        Limit both the width and height of the video to value. The other
        dimension is computed so that the device aspect-ratio is preserved.
        Default is 0 (unlimited).

    -M
        Same as --mouse=uhid, or --mouse=aoa if --otg is set.

    --max-fps=value
        Limit the frame rate of screen capture (officially supported since
        Android 10, but may work on earlier versions).

    --mouse=mode
        Select how to send mouse inputs to the device.
        Possible values are "disabled", "sdk", "uhid" and "aoa".
        "disabled" does not send mouse inputs to the device.
        "sdk" uses the Android system API to deliver mouse eventsto
        applications.
        "uhid" simulates a physical HID mouse using the Linux UHID kernel module
        on the device.
        "aoa" simulates a physical mouse using the AOAv2 protocol. It may only
        work over USB.
        In "uhid" and "aoa" modes, the computer mouse is captured to control the
        device directly (relative mouse mode).
        LAlt, LSuper or RSuper toggle the capture mode, to give control of the
        mouse back to the computer.
        Also see --keyboard and --gamepad.

    --mouse-bind=xxxx[:xxxx]
        Configure bindings of secondary clicks.
        The argument must be one or two sequences (separated by ':') of exactly
        4 characters, one for each secondary click (in order: right click,
        middle click, 4th click, 5th click).
        The first sequence defines the primary bindings, used when a mouse
        button is pressed alone. The second sequence defines the secondary
        bindings, used when a mouse button is pressed while the Shift key is
        held.
        If the second sequence of bindings is omitted, then it is the same as
        the first one.
        Each character must be one of the following:
         '+': forward the click to the device
         '-': ignore the click
         'b': trigger shortcut BACK (or turn screen on if off)
         'h': trigger shortcut HOME
         's': trigger shortcut APP_SWITCH
         'n': trigger shortcut "expand notification panel"
        Default is 'bhsn:++++' for SDK mouse, and '++++:bhsn' for AOA and UHID.

    -n, --no-control
        Disable device control (mirror the device in read-only).

    -N, --no-playback
        Disable video and audio playback on the computer (equivalent to
        --no-video-playback --no-audio-playback).

    --new-display[=[<width>x<height>][/<dpi>]]
        Create a new display with the specified resolution and density. If not
        provided, they default to the main display dimensions and DPI.
        Examples:
            --new-display=1920x1080
            --new-display=1920x1080/420  # force 420 dpi
            --new-display         # main display size and density
            --new-display=/240    # main display size and 240 dpi

    --no-audio
        Disable audio forwarding.

    --no-audio-playback
        Disable audio playback on the computer.

    --no-cleanup
        By default, scrcpy removes the server binary from the device and
        restores the device state (show touches, stay awake and power mode) on
        exit.
        This option disables this cleanup.

    --no-clipboard-autosync
        By default, scrcpy automatically synchronizes the computer clipboard to
        the device clipboard before injecting Ctrl+v, and the device clipboard
        to the computer clipboard whenever it changes.
        This option disables this automatic synchronization.

    --no-downsize-on-error
        By default, on MediaCodec error, scrcpy automatically tries again with a
        lower definition.
        This option disables this behavior.

    --no-key-repeat
        Do not forward repeated key events when a key is held down.

    --no-mipmaps
        If the renderer is OpenGL 3.0+ or OpenGL ES 2.0+, then mipmaps are
        automatically generated to improve downscaling quality. This option
        disables the generation of mipmaps.

    --no-mouse-hover
        Do not forward mouse hover (mouse motion without any clicks) events.

    --no-power-on
        Do not power on the device on start.

    --no-vd-system-decorations
        Disable virtual display system decorations flag.

    --no-video
        Disable video forwarding.

    --no-video-playback
        Disable video playback on the computer.

    --no-window
        Disable scrcpy window. Implies --no-video-playback and --no-control.

    --orientation=value
        Same as --display-orientation=value --record-orientation=value.

    --otg
        Run in OTG mode: simulate physical keyboard and mouse, as if the
        computer keyboard and mouse were plugged directly to the device via an
        OTG cable.
        In this mode, adb (USB debugging) is not necessary, and mirroring is
        disabled.
        LAlt, LSuper or RSuper toggle the mouse capture mode, to give control of
        the mouse back to the computer.
        Keyboard and mouse may be disabled separately using--keyboard=disabled
        and --mouse=disabled.
        It may only work over USB.
        See --keyboard, --mouse and --gamepad.

    -p, --port=port[:port]
        Set the TCP port (range) used by the client to listen.
        Default is 27183:27199.

    --pause-on-exit[=mode]
        Configure pause on exit. Possible values are "true" (always pause on
        exit), "false" (never pause on exit) and "if-error" (pause only if an
        error occurred).
        This is useful to prevent the terminal window from automatically
        closing, so that error messages can be read.
        Default is "false".
        Passing the option without argument is equivalent to passing "true".

    --power-off-on-close
        Turn the device screen off when closing scrcpy.

    --prefer-text
        Inject alpha characters and space as text events instead of key events.
        This avoids issues when combining multiple keys to enter a special
        character, but breaks the expected behavior of alpha keys in games
        (typically WASD).

    --print-fps
        Start FPS counter, to print framerate logs to the console. It can be
        started or stopped at any time with MOD+i.

    --push-target=path
        Set the target directory for pushing files to the device by drag & drop.
        It is passed as is to "adb push".
        Default is "/sdcard/Download/".

    -r, --record=file.mp4
        Record screen to file.
        The format is determined by the --record-format option if set, or by the
        file extension.

    --raw-key-events
        Inject key events for all input keys, and ignore text events.

    --record-format=format
        Force recording format (mp4, mkv, m4a, mka, opus, aac, flac or wav).

    --record-orientation=value
        Set the record orientation.
        Possible values are 0, 90, 180 and 270. The number represents the
        clockwise rotation in degrees.
        Default is 0.

    --render-driver=name
        Request SDL to use the given render driver (this is just a hint).
        Supported names are currently "direct3d", "opengl", "opengles2",
        "opengles", "metal" and "software".
        <https://wiki.libsdl.org/SDL_HINT_RENDER_DRIVER>

    --require-audio
        By default, scrcpy mirrors only the video when audio capture fails on
        the device. This option makes scrcpy fail if audio is enabled but does
        not work.

    -s, --serial=serial
        The device serial number. Mandatory only if several devices are
        connected to adb.

    -S, --turn-screen-off
        Turn the device screen off immediately.

    --screen-off-timeout=seconds
        Set the screen off timeout while scrcpy is running (restore the initial
        value on exit).

    --shortcut-mod=key[+...][,...]
        Specify the modifiers to use for scrcpy shortcuts.
        Possible keys are "lctrl", "rctrl", "lalt", "ralt", "lsuper" and
        "rsuper".
        Several shortcut modifiers can be specified, separated by ','.
        For example, to use either LCtrl or LSuper for scrcpy shortcuts, pass
        "lctrl,lsuper".
        Default is "lalt,lsuper" (left-Alt or left-Super).

    --start-app=name
        Start an Android app, by its exact package name.
        Add a '?' prefix to select an app whose name starts with the given name,
        case-insensitive (retrieving app names on the device may take some
        time):
            scrcpy --start-app=?firefox
        Add a '+' prefix to force-stop before starting the app:
            scrcpy --new-display --start-app=+org.mozilla.firefox
        Both prefixes can be used, in that order:
            scrcpy --start-app=+?firefox

    -t, --show-touches
        Enable "show touches" on start, restore the initial value on exit.
        It only shows physical touches (not clicks from scrcpy).

    --tcpip[=[+]ip[:port]]
        Configure and connect the device over TCP/IP.
        If a destination address is provided, then scrcpy connects to this
        address before starting. The device must listen on the given TCP port
        (default is 5555).
        If no destination address is provided, then scrcpy attempts to find the
        IP address of the current device (typically connected over USB), enables
        TCP/IP mode, then connects to this address before starting.
        Prefix the address with a '+' to force a reconnection.

    --time-limit=seconds
        Set the maximum mirroring time, in seconds.

    --tunnel-host=ip
        Set the IP address of the adb tunnel to reach the scrcpy server. This
        option automatically enables --force-adb-forward.
        Default is localhost.

    --tunnel-port=port
        Set the TCP port of the adb tunnel to reach the scrcpy server. This
        option automatically enables --force-adb-forward.
        Default is 0 (not forced): the local port used for establishing the
        tunnel will be used.

    -v, --version
        Print the version of scrcpy.

    -V, --verbosity=value
        Set the log level (verbose, debug, info, warn or error).
        Default is info.

    --v4l2-sink=/dev/videoN
        Output to v4l2loopback device.
        This feature is only available on Linux.

    --v4l2-buffer=ms
        Add a buffering delay (in milliseconds) before pushing frames. This
        increases latency to compensate for jitter.
        This option is similar to --video-buffer, but specific to V4L2 sink.
        Default is 0 (no buffering).
        This option is only available on Linux.

    --video-buffer=ms
        Add a buffering delay (in milliseconds) before displaying video frames.
        This increases latency to compensate for jitter.
        Default is 0 (no buffering).

    --video-codec=name
        Select a video codec (h264, h265 or av1).
        Default is h264.

    --video-codec-options=key[:type]=value[,...]
        Set a list of comma-separated key:type=value options for the device
        video encoder.
        The possible values for 'type' are 'int' (default), 'long', 'float' and
        'string'.
        The list of possible codec options is available in the Android
        documentation:
        <https://d.android.com/reference/android/media/MediaFormat>

    --video-encoder=name
        Use a specific MediaCodec video encoder (depending on the codec provided
        by --video-codec).
        The available encoders can be listed by --list-encoders.

    --video-source=source
        Select the video source (display or camera).
        Camera mirroring requires Android 12+.
        Default is display.

    -w, --stay-awake
        Keep the device on while scrcpy is running, when the device is plugged
        in.

    --window-borderless
        Disable window decorations (display borderless window).

    --window-title=text
        Set a custom window title.

    --window-x=value
        Set the initial window horizontal position.
        Default is "auto".

    --window-y=value
        Set the initial window vertical position.
        Default is "auto".

    --window-width=value
        Set the initial window width.
        Default is 0 (automatic).

    --window-height=value
        Set the initial window height.
        Default is 0 (automatic).

Shortcuts:

    In the following list, MOD is the shortcut modifier. By default, it's (left)
    Alt or (left) Super, but it can be configured by --shortcut-mod (see above).

    MOD+f
        Switch fullscreen mode

    MOD+Left
        Rotate display left

    MOD+Right
        Rotate display right

    MOD+Shift+Left
    MOD+Shift+Right
        Flip display horizontally

    MOD+Shift+Up
    MOD+Shift+Down
        Flip display vertically

    MOD+z
        Pause or re-pause display

    MOD+Shift+z
        Unpause display

    MOD+Shift+r
        Reset video capture/encoding

    MOD+g
        Resize window to 1:1 (pixel-perfect)

    MOD+w
    Double-click on black borders
        Resize window to remove black borders

    MOD+h
    Middle-click
        Click on HOME

    MOD+b
    MOD+Backspace
    Right-click (when screen is on)
        Click on BACK

    MOD+s
    4th-click
        Click on APP_SWITCH

    MOD+m
        Click on MENU

    MOD+Up
        Click on VOLUME_UP

    MOD+Down
        Click on VOLUME_DOWN

    MOD+p
        Click on POWER (turn screen on/off)

    Right-click (when screen is off)
        Power on

    MOD+o
        Turn device screen off (keep mirroring)

    MOD+Shift+o
        Turn device screen on

    MOD+r
        Rotate device screen

    MOD+n
    5th-click
        Expand notification panel

    MOD+Shift+n
        Collapse notification panel

    MOD+c
        Copy to clipboard (inject COPY keycode, Android >= 7 only)

    MOD+x
        Cut to clipboard (inject CUT keycode, Android >= 7 only)

    MOD+v
        Copy computer clipboard to device, then paste (inject PASTE keycode,
        Android >= 7 only)

    MOD+Shift+v
        Inject computer clipboard text as a sequence of key events

    MOD+k
        Open keyboard settings on the device (for HID keyboard only)

    MOD+i
        Enable/disable FPS counter (print frames/second in logs)

    Ctrl+click-and-move
        Pinch-to-zoom and rotate from the center of the screen

    Shift+click-and-move
        Tilt vertically (slide with 2 fingers)

    Ctrl+Shift+click-and-move
        Tilt horizontally (slide with 2 fingers)

    Drag & drop APK file
        Install APK from computer

    Drag & drop non-APK file
        Push file to device (see --push-target)

Environment variables:

    ADB
        Path to adb executable

    ANDROID_SERIAL
        Device serial to use if no selector (-s, -d, -e or --tcpip=<addr>) is
        specified

    SCRCPY_ICON_PATH
        Path to the program icon

    SCRCPY_SERVER_PATH
        Path to the server binary

Exit status:

      0  Normal program termination
      1  Start failure
      2  Device disconnected while running
